原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译    @少年影视派   斑驳   油腻希
翻译    洗七里   Flora哎呀呀    无需美容觉赛太公
校对    新浪微博@赛太公
时间轴   三水
后期    只想躺着等天上掉钱的瓜瓜
总监    生无可恋瓜
家  庭
摩  登
第十一季 第一集
南极
坐标
又没有邮件
No mail. Again.
菲尔·邓菲
嘿  传送门  联系爸爸
Hey, Portal, call Dad.
♪ 当利率降下来 ♪
♪ When the rates fall ♪
♪ 他们会再融资 ♪
♪ They will refi ♪
♪ 那就是房产经纪人的摇篮曲 ♪
♪ And that's the Realtor's lullaby ♪
乔治  拜托
George, please!
他们怎么还在哭啊
Why are they still crying?
是不是因为他们知道自己是小胖子了
Do you think they know they're chubby?
虽然花了不少时间
It took us a while,
但我们终于给孩子取好名字了
but we finally named our babies.
这是"茵素"
This is Poppy,
因为我最喜欢的花就是罂粟花
because that's my favorite flower.
这是乔治
And this is George,
因为他出生时看上去很好奇
because he came out looking curious.
取自歌手博伊·乔治
You know, like Boy George.
实际上是出自《好奇猴乔治》
传送门  接通吧
Oh, hey, Portal, answer.
嗨  艾丽克斯
Hi, Alex!
我的冰雪女王宝贝怎么样啊
How's my little ice queen?
我上高中时就不喜欢别人叫我冰雪女王
Didn't love being called that in high school,
现在也不喜欢
don't love it now.
你好啊  宝贝  总是有很多人问我
Hey, honey. Um, people keep asking --
能再跟我说说你在做什么吗
tell me again what you're doing?
探测南极大陆地下中微子的存在
Detecting the presence of neutrinos beneath the South Pole.
好吧  打住  我还是继续告诉他们
Yeah, you -- you can stop. I'm just gonna keep telling them
你在搜寻雪怪吧
you're searching for the snow monster.
不是吧  艾丽克斯
Seriously, Alex?
你就不能下楼来跟我们聊吗
You can't come downstairs to talk to us?
我已经离开一个月了
I've been gone for a month.
等等  所以下水道卡着的是我的头发吗
Wait. So, that's my hair in the drain?
宝贝  你那边一切都好吧
Honey, is everything okay?
你看上去有点悲伤
You look a little sad.
不  没有
Oh, no, no.
我是之前有点悲伤  脸被冻住塑形了
I was sad earlier, and my face froze that way.
但我不后悔拒掉
But no regrets about
洛杉矶的科技公司那份轻松的工作
turning down that cushy tech job in L.A.
我是说  没错  我想念比尔了
I mean, yeah, I miss Bill
以及有其他女性同事在周围的安全感
and the safety of other women around,
但外公说得对
but Grandpa was right.
现在正是享受冒险的大好光阴
This is the time of life to have an adventure.
我是不是联系得不是时候
Is this a bad time?
不  不  这已经成为我们的新常态了
Oh, no. No, this is our new normal.
-是啊  -我们就没睡过觉了
- Yeah. ‭ - We never sleep.
我太理解被剥夺睡眠的痛苦了
Well, I know all about sleep deprivation.
这里是极昼  太阳永远不落
The sun never sets here,
-所以我已经好几天没睡过觉了  -好吧  真有趣
- so I've been up for days. - Yeah, that's fun.
-真好  宝贝  -我现在醒着都能做梦
- Really nice, honey. - I dream awake now.
稍等下  海莉
Hang on a second. Haley.
海莉  我知道你铁了心坚持母乳喂养
Haley, I know that you are committed to breastfeeding
信奉这本书
and the book,
但我觉得你是时候考虑使用配方奶粉了
but I think it's time that you considered formula.
那将有助于婴儿的睡眠
It will help the babies sleep,
儿童医生也说那是绝对健康的
and the pediatrician said it is perfectly healthy.
我就是活生生的证据  我从小就是喝奶粉长大的
I'm living proof. I was a formula baby --
-6个月时嘴里牙就长满了  -就是啊
- had a full set of teeth at six months. - Yeah.
但是这书上说...
But the book says --
又是这本书
Uch, the book.
你对我的书有什么意见
What do you have against my book?
这本书名叫《你父母的育儿方式全是错的》
It is called "Your Parents Did Everything Wrong."
古迪医生是个享有盛名的小儿生活指导师
Dr. Goode is a celebrated pediatric life coach.
你能调低一点你身上的消极性吗
And can you tone down the negativity?
第六章说这可能会引起对花生的过敏
Chapter six says that it can cause an allergy to peanuts.
天啊  小孩子都应该有史努比的陪伴长大
Oh, man, no kid should grow up without Snoopy.
史努比出自《花生漫画》
听上去像是个疯狂的清晨
Sounds like a crazy morning.
我好怀念这种生活
I miss those.
我的研究搭档英格瓦不会说英语
My research partner, Yngvar, doesn't speak English.
是我吗干的
Is me who did that?
除了他从《凡人琐事》的重播集中学到的台词
Except for what he learned from reruns of "Family Matters."
各位
Guys!
有时候那真的有点烦人
So that can be a little annoying
因为你的研究搭档竟然不会说你的语言
having a research partner not speak your language,
不过我可以学他的语言
but I could also try and learn his language,
我也真的去学了
which I have.
敢吵醒他们  我就杀了你
Wake them, and I kill you.
更像西班牙语一些
‭More Spanish.
如果这是在玩角色扮演
If this is role-playing,
我想扮演"被恶心到的儿子"一角
I'd like to play the part of disgusted son.
我要为我的狗窝公司做个宣传视频
I'm making a promo video for my dog-bed company.
当然了  领衔主演是斯黛拉
And Stella's the star, of course.
今天我们要给它录配音
Today we're recording her voice.
我亲自配西班牙语版本
And I am doing the Spanish version.
导演是谁
Who's directing it?
我不知道  大概是我吧
I don't know. Me, I guess.
这可真让我感到很受伤
Wow, that's a punch in the gut.
怎么了  曼尼  你想来执导吗
Why, Manny? Do you want to direct it?
为什么不行
Why not?
有些最出色的艺术家也是拍广告出身的
Some of our best artists started out making commercials.
我比斯派克·琼斯或吉列尔莫·德尔托罗更出色吗
Am I better than Spike Jonze or Guillermo del Toro?
没有
Nope.
听着  通常我都会编个原因
Listen, normally I would just
说你导不了
cook up some fake reason why you couldn't direct it,
但这个情况下  我有个真正的理由
but in this case, I have a real excuse.
你的前女友雪莉
Your old girlfriend, Sherry,
为斯黛拉配音
is the voice of Stella.
杰  你怎么能这样
Jay, how could you?
雪莉可是在他提出了要娶她的想法后
After she broke his heart when she got repulsed
被吓跑并伤透了他的心呢
by the idea of getting married to him?
更多的是不知所措  不是吓跑吧
More overwhelmed than repulsed,
我记得是这样
as I remember it.
她已经在我们网站上
She's already on our website
为斯黛拉配音了
as Stella's voice.
现在改变
Changing that now
会让我们的粉丝不好接受
could be jarring for our fans.
就比如他们把我的GPS
Like when they made
变成女版英式口音
my GPS lady British.
我情愿迷路
I'd rather be lost
也不要被一个臭屁鬼导航
than talked down to by a snob!
拜托了  杰
Please, Jay.
我需要证明我已经放下她了
I need to prove to myself that I'm over her,
我可以不受其影响 做得很专业
that I can rise above it and be professional.
好吧  但如果你的感情
Fine, but if your emotions
阻碍了这个作品
get in the way of this production,
你就再没有机会为狗窝做广告
you will never work in dog-bed commercials again.
别担心
Don't worry.
我唯一的热情
My only passion
就是帮你实现你充满创造力的想象
is helping you realize your creative vision.
今天结束前  雪莉就会是我的了
By day's end, Sherry will be mine.
不  我们今天庆祝
Oh, no, which icon's birthday
哪个偶像的生日
are we celebrating today?
劳伦·白考尔
Uh, Lauren Bacall's.
等下我们会在她的墓碑前撒郁金香
We're dropping tulips by her grave later,
但这不是为了她的生日
but that's not what this is.
不  我有些迷途青年学生要来
No, I'm having some at-risk students over.
-你们问为什么  -我不想知道
- Why, you ask? - ‭I'm good.
因为我想和这些孩子建立情感
Well, 'cause I want to bond with these kids.
我想让他们知道
I want them to know that even though
即便整个世界放弃了他们
the rest of the world's given up on them,
我也不会
I haven't.
我不想只做他们的副[坏]校长
I don't want to just be their Vice Principal.
我想做他们的好校长
I want to be their nice principal.
我不敢相信你让此发生
I can't believe you let this happen.
我不知道他会玩文字哏
I didn't know there'd be wordplay.
小卡让我作为助理检察官和他的学生聊聊
Cam asked me to speak to his students as an Assistant DA,
用执法机关的角度与他们交流一下
give them the perspective of law enforcement.
事实上我一直在找个机会
Truth is, I have been looking for an opportunity
展示我的新勋章
to show off my new badge.
即使是最硬气的罪犯
Even the most hardened criminals
看到也会发抖
shudder when they get a gander at --
千万别刮伤了
Please don't be scratched!
♪ 我腿上放着班卓琴 ♪
♪ With a banjo on my knee ♪
我不在乎这些孩子们做过什么
I don't care what these kids did.
-这惩罚太惨无人道了  -我知道
- This is cruel. ‭- I know.
一个玩摇滚的副校长
A vice principal that plays rock 'n' roll.
我是不是不太一样  是的
Am I a little different? Yes, I am.
我不像你们生命中其他成年人
I'm not like the other adults in your life
他们等着你们把事情搞糟
that are just waiting for you to mess up
然后对你们指指点点
so they can point the finger at you.
我不想指指点点[指交]小孩
I don't want to finger a bunch of kids.
这不是我欢乐的来源
That's not how I get my jollies.
小卡  小卡
Cam. Cam.
我知道那种感觉
I know what it's like.
我曾经上学时也遇到问题
I had issues in school,
我也被人各种指指点点[指交]
and I was fingered left and right.
让我告诉你们  那感觉很难受
And let me tell you, it did not feel good.
米奇尔  我们是不是应该录下来
Oh, Mitchell, should we be recording this?
是的  不然我说了别人都不信
Oh, yes, no one's gonna believe me.
这需要多久  塔克先生
How long is this gonna take, Mr. Tucker?
塔克先生是你们的酷副校长
Oh, now, Mr. Tucker's the cool vice principal at school.
在我家里
Here at my house
请叫我小卡
call me Cam.
好吗
Okay?
这是米奇尔
And this is Mitchell.
他是一位助理检察官
He's an Assistant District Attorney,
他是我们的特邀发言人
and he is our guest speaker.
他白[人]到像透明的一样
He's so white he's see-through.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我们居住在一个受法律约束的社会
We live in a society bound by laws.
对吧
Okay?
而法律分隔了秩序与混乱
They're all that stand between order and chaos.
而违反法律的人
And those who violate those laws
将会看到法律的这一面...
wind up staring at the business end of --
它不见了
It's gone!
什么  你身上的聚光灯吗
What, the spotlight on you?
不是  我的小丑雕塑
No, my porcelain clown figurine.
它本应该在这个桌子上的
It's supposed to be on this table.
它一直在这个桌子上
It's always on this table.
你们当中有人偷了它
One of you stole it!
居然还在劳伦·白考尔生日这天
And on Lauren Bacall's birthday?
小卡  小卡  冷静
Cam. Cam. R-Relax.
今天不就是为了不要对他们先入为主吗
Uh, isn't the whole point of today not to prejudge them?
得了  米奇尔  他们是垃圾
Oh, please, Mitchell. They're trash.
我知道  他们也知道
I know it. They know it.
每个人都知道
Everybody knows it.
♪ 欢迎回家  我亲爱的宝贝们 ♪
♪ Welcome home, my sweet babies ♪
♪ 交好保证金后  拿钥匙 ♪
♪ After escrow, get the key ♪
求你别唱那首歌好吗
Please don't sing that song.
抱歉  但这首好过《爸爸去房产估价会了》
Sorry, it's better than "Pop Goes the Appraisal."
妈妈  你在干什么
‭Mom, what are you doing?
快停下  书上说不应该在宝宝午睡时
Stop it. The book says you're not supposed to
跟他们眼神有接触
make eye contact during nap time.
他们只是婴儿  又不是片场的男神约翰尼·德普
They're babies, not Johnny Depp on a film set.
♪ 房屋参观时段为中午到下午5点 ♪
♪ Open house, noon to 5:00 ♪
♪ 这间需要修缮的房子真可爱 ♪
♪ Such a charming fixer-upper ♪
怎么样了
H-o-ow's it going?
还在哭
Still crying.
你没跟他们发生眼神接触吧
You didn't make eye contact, did you?
并没有那种说法  菲尔
That can't be a thing, Phil.
而且我有点听烦了
And I'm getting a little sick
海莉总暗示我们不会抚养小孩
of Haley insinuating that we don't know how to raise kids.
她说的肯定不是我
She can't be saying that about me.
我三十岁期间有五年都拿来跟孩子们盖毯子堡垒
I spent half my 30s in blanket forts with those kids.
知道吗
You know what?
你得去把她哄睡着
You need to get her to go to sleep
我才能用正确的方式把宝宝们哄睡着
so I can put those babies down the right way.
用我们的方式
Our way.
她现在都被逼疯了  我怎么才能哄她去睡觉
She's crazed right now. How am I supposed to get her to sleep?
我不知道啊  她小时候你是怎么做的
I don't know. How did you do it when she was a kid?
爸爸  药店不是在那个方向吗
Dad, isn't the drugstore that way?
是没错  但那边施工
It is, but there's construction,
我只能...  绕个路
so I got to -- got to go around.
车里是不是好热呀
Is it warm in here?
我觉得还好啊
I feel fine.
对了  我最近发现了一个新电台
You know, uh, I just discovered this new station
叫"世界之风"
called "Winds of the World."
这个很棒
Ooh, this is -- this is a good one.
假如你闭上眼睛
If you close your eyes,
就会感觉自己正身处...
it feels like you're right there in, um...
"开阔大草原"
"Open Prairie."
试试  你在后座眯眼休息会儿吧
Try it. You should get some rest back there.
我不困
I'm not sleepy.
你不用睡着啦
Well, you don't have to sleep.
就是闭目养神一下
Just, uh -- Just rest your eyes.
人家不想嘛
Uch. I don't wanna.
你发脾气只是因为你太累了
You are just grumpy 'cause you're overtired.
别再说我累了好不好
Stop saying I'm tired!
好的
Okay.
我知道了
I know.
我们来列举一下
Let's make a list
明天都想做些什么事吧
of all the things we want to do tomorrow.
我嘛  我打算吃华夫饼
I am, uh -- I'm gonna have some waffles,
出门
uh, go outside,
列出我所有朋友的名字
uh, make a list of all my friends' names.
有...  邮差
There's, uh, the mailman...
开...  冰淇淋店的那位女士
the lady with the ice cream...house...
当你躺在斯黛拉的狗床上
Cuando te acuestas en una cama de perro por Stella,
你会感到被爱环抱
sabes que eres amado.
非常棒  老婆  录好了
It's perfect, honey. We got it.
她永远都说不好了
She's never gonna get there.
我去公园里找个拉丁裔保姆来配音好了
I'll ask one of the nannies in the park to do it
就下次我照顾乔的时候
next time I take Joe.
她们爱死我了
They love me.
我每次去她们都非要送我粉蒸肉带走
I can never get out of there without a bag of tamales.
我们的巨星来了
Well, there's our star!
杰你好啊  我超喜欢剧本  好有趣哦
Hey, Jay. Love the script, so fun!
曼尼
Manny.
我不知道你会来
I didn't know you'd be here.
我是你的导演
I'm your director.
我们之间用不着感到尴尬
No reason it has to be awkward.
只要你在"开拍"和"卡"之间
As long as you do everything I say
完全按我说的去做
between "Action" and "Cut."
说到开拍
Speaking of which,
我最近"开啪"了不少次呢
I've been getting quite a bit of action.
卡  听着  这场地按小时收我租金的
And cut. Look, I'm renting this joint by the hour.
我们赶快开工行吗
Can we just do this?
你好  歌洛莉亚
Hi, Gloria.
雪莉你好  演出顺利[摔断腿]
Hi, Sherry. Break your legs.
雪莉  你准备好就随时开始吧
Okay, Sherry, whenever you're ready.
天惹  我在公园玩了一整天的接球  挖地
Boy, am I tired after a day of playing fetch, digging,
和闻其他狗狗之后  真是累毙了耶
and sniffing other dogs at the park.
要是有张美国制造的床就好啦
If only there were an American-made bed...
真抱歉  刚才表现太糟了
Ugh, I'm so sorry. That was terrible.
曼尼  我们重头来过好吗
Manny, can we start over?
我从没有过停止爱...
I never stopped..
你是指广告  好
You mean the commercial. Yes.
不过  你刚才表现得很到位
Although, that was exquisite.
我都相信你真是条狗了
I believed that you're a dog.
我是歌洛莉亚啦
It's Gloria.
而你  真是丢人丢到家了
And you, you're embarrassing yourself.
-你在说什么呢  -你想赢回她的芳心
- What are you talking about? - ‭You're trying to win her back.
纽扣打开了几颗  喷了香水
The unbuttoned shirt, the cologne,
还赞美她刚才那乏味的表演
the praising of her pedestrian performance.
-你不会成功的  曼尼  -为什么
- It's not gonna work, Manny. ‭- Why not?
因为如果你希望别人喜欢你
Because if you want someone to like you,
就得让他们想要得到你的认可才行
you need to make them want your approval.
妈妈  这种老招早就被用过八百遍了
Mom, that's a tired, old way of thinking
不会有用的
that doesn't work.
给你
Here you go.
你觉得这杯东西有什么问题
What do you think is wrong with this?
见鬼  忘记放柠檬了  宝贝抱歉
Damn it, the lemon! I'm sorry, baby.
从头再来一遍
L-Let's start from the top.
这次语速别那么慢
And this time, not so slow.
更强硬点
Stronger.
主张要坚决  曼尼尔
Assert yourself, Manuel.
你说的话我一个字都听不清
And I couldn't understand a word you were saying.
嘴里不要像含着卤蛋
Try to get the marbles out of your mouth.
抱歉
Oh, sorry.
好的  你有要求尽管提
Yeah, whatever you need.
没准真能成
Wow, maybe this could work.
反正你都站着了  我肩膀有点僵
While you're up, my shoulders are a little tight.
帮我揉揉好吗
You mind getting in there?
我的双手接近你的颈动脉你还有命吗
I don't think you want my hands that close to your neck.
我邀请你们到我家来
I invite you into my home,
可你们就这样报答我
and this is how you repay me?
我知道你们是怎么想的
Oh, I know what you were thinking.
"他过着帝王般的生活  不差一个小雕塑"
"He'll never miss it. He lives like a king."
我们没偷你的破小丑
We didn't take your stupid clown!
你怎么知道是小丑  苏西
Interesting you know it's a clown, Suzie!
你都说过三次了  卡梅隆
You said it three times, Cameron.
请叫我副校长塔克
It's Vice Principal Tucker!
放尊重点  我可不是你妈的鸡头
Show some respect. I'm not your mom's pimp.
好了  小卡
Okay, Cam.
小卡  我知道你很喜欢小摆件
Cam, I-I know you like your tchotchkes,
但你叫孩子们来不是为了建立情感吗
but aren't these kids here so you can bond?
艾丽克斯  一切还好吗
Hey, Alex. Everything okay?
是的  或许是我小题大做了
Yeah, yeah. I-I'm probably overreacting.
我之前试着和这的一个科学家交朋友
It's just I tried to make friends with one of the scientists,
但我们语言不通
but there's a language gap.
他误会了  吻了我
He misunderstood and kissed me.
所以现在有点尴尬
So it's a little awkward now.
听起来真有趣
Uh-huh, that sounds fun.
什么  才不是
What?! It's not.
我有点想回家
I kind of want to come home,
可我来这让外公那么激动
but Grandpa was so excited about me doing this,
我不想让他失望
and I don't want to disappoint him.
你总让他失望
Hey, you've disappointed him a lot.
那是种什么体验
What was that like?
艾丽克斯  我为此纠结过许多年
Ohh, Alex, I struggled with this for years,
但我终于悟懂了
but I-I finally learned
最重要的事是
that the most important thing is --
艾丽克斯  替我跟圣诞老人打个招呼
Hey, Alex! Say "Hi" to Santa Claus.
-再见  -这是南极不是北极
- Bye! - ‭I'm at the South Po-
好了  我想好要怎么做了
Okay. Alright, I've decided what I'm gonna do.
我要对其中一个孩子发起猛攻
I'm gonna turn the heat up on one of the kids.
那孩子要是凶手就会承认
If they did it, they'll confess.
假如不是  真凶
If not, the actual criminal...
就会内疚自首
will feel guilty and step forward.
所以咱整个周六就不干别的了吗
So, this is gonna be our whole Saturday?
好吧
Okay.
买单车干嘛  根本没机会骑
Why-Why did we even buy bikes?
是你偷了他的破小丑  对吗
You took his stupid, little clown, didn't you?
你们这代人如此残缺又愤世嫉俗
I find it sad that your generation
太悲哀了
is so damaged and cynical.
那是几天前的事
It happened a few days ago.
我讨厌那玩意
I hated that thing.
必须处理掉
It had to go.
不然他会凑成一整套收藏
I mean, that's how collections start.
我也不喜欢那个猫咪保温罩
I wasn't crazy about the cat cozy, either.
但我从未想过
But I never intended
小卡会错怪那些可怜孩子之一
for Cam to blame it on one of those poor kids.
我本想让保洁阿姨背这个锅的
I mean, I was just gonna pin it on the cleaning lady.
你把它藏哪了  小白崽子
Where's it at, Wonderbread?!
我不知道你在说什么
Uh, I don't know what you're talking about,
塔克老师  我发誓
Mr. Tucker. I-I swear.
好了好了
Okay. Okay.
我们都喘口气
Let's just, uh -- Let's all take a breath
回想一下基本的法律常识  好吗
and just remember some of the basics of the law, okay?
在被证明有罪之前  我们都是无辜的
We're all innocent until proven guilty.
怎么说我也是个身上带着...
Take it from someone who is packing one of --
见鬼  我把警徽忘在厨房了
oh, dang it. Ooh, I left it in the kitchen.
你们先别动
Okay, stay right there.
-太逊了  我们走  -不行
- This is lame. Let's bounce. - Okay, no.
在我找到小雕像前谁也不准走
No one is bouncing until I get my figurine.
但我必须尽快回家
But I have to get home soon.
我读过你的档案  贝琳达
I've read your file, Belinda.
根本没人在乎你  也不在乎你去哪
No one knows or cares where you are.
喝光
And...
搞定
done!
为什么  为什么
Oh, why?! Why?!
这是怎么回事
What is going on?
宝宝们怎么还醒着
How are they still awake?
我吸尘器也开了  奶粉也喂了
I tried the vacuum. I tried formula.
我什么都试过了
I tried everything.
还有办法
Not quite.
是时候拿出
It is time to break out...
大杀器了
the big guns.
我知道海莉不准用安抚奶嘴
I know Haley banned pacifiers,
但我买这些的时候
but I bought these
还以为她会是那种有哏的妈妈
when I thought she was gonna be a fun mom.
来吧
Let's do it.
快看
Look at that.
药到病除
It's working already.
老式育儿胜利了
Old-school parenting for the win.
他们马上就会睡着的
They'll be asleep in no time,
除非看到对方
unless they see each other.
-那就会笑到停不下来了  -是啊
- Then they won't be able to stop laughing. ‭- Yes.
什么情况
What the hell?
奶粉  奶嘴
Formula? Pacifiers?
你们在逗我吗
Are you kidding me?!
这可真是一种清奇的方式来表达"妈妈  谢谢你
This is a very weird way of saying, "Thank you, Mother,
安顿好我的宝宝
for settling down my babies.
我还有很多要向你学习"
I have a lot to learn from you."
我说的你一个字都没听
You ignored everything I asked of you!
海莉  不要对你妈妈这么过分
Haley, don't be so hard on your mom.
还有你
Ohh, you!
这奶嘴一看就是你的风格
Those pacifiers have you written all over them.
宝宝们不该抽烟  反差萌啊
Babies aren't supposed to smoke!
你们怎么能背着我做这种事呢
How could you sneak behind my back like that?
宝贝  我们就是想帮你
Honey, we were just trying to help.
好吧  你没帮上
Well, you didn't.
书里说85%用奶嘴的宝宝
The book says 85% of pacifier users
长大后会变成猫奴
grow up to be cat people.
真不敢相信我会这么说  你真的不能再看书了
I can't believe I'm saying this, but you need to stop reading.
然后呢
And do what?
然后  靠我的母性本能吗
Do what? Rely on my instincts?
我没有本能  这就是问题
I don't have any. That is the problem!
宝贝  每个人都有本能
Honey, everybody has instincts.
是吗  我有吗
Oh, do I?
我一直在等着本能自己发动
Because I keep waiting for them to kick in,
但它没有
and they haven't.
我觉得它永远也不会发动了
And I don't think that they ever will.
我只是  可能我就是不应该成为一个妈妈
I just -- Maybe I'm just not meant to be a mom.
宝贝  你当然可以成为一个妈妈
Sweetie, of course you're meant to be a mom.
听着  感觉到不知所措很正常  真的
Listen, it is normal to feel overwhelmed. Really.
最好的父母都是担心自己做得
It -- The best parents are the ones who worry
不够好的父母
they're doing it wrong.
爱人也一样
Same goes for lovers.
等等  宝宝们还在沙发上吗
Wait, are the babies still on the couch?
他们肯定没事啦
Oh, I'm sure they're fine.
门锁住了  宝宝们这个时候会滚来滚去了
It's locked. Babies start rolling over at this age.
你有钥匙吗
Oh. ‭Do you have a key?
放里面了  不过我很久以前在外面藏了一把
Uh, it's inside, but I hid one out here years ago.
放在
It's in, um...
一块假的石头里
It's in a fake rock.
找不到了
Can't -- Can't find it.
那块石头太真了
It's -- It's too realistic.
我为什么要加钱买逼真的好货
Why did I spring for the good one?
我必须进去
I have to get in there.
海莉  海莉  你要干什么
Haley! Haley, what are you doing?!
宝贝  宝贝  小心
Honey. Honey, be careful.
那个屋顶每爬必摔啊
It's impossible not to fall off of that roof!
茵素  乔治  妈妈来了
Poppy! George! Mommy's coming!
我觉得这看上去很母性本能
Those sure look like mom instincts to me!
你是天生的好妈妈
You're a natural!
现在知道她以前是怎么在宵禁后溜进来的了
Now we know how she used to sneak in after curfew.
也知道今年该让谁来挂圣诞彩灯了
And who's hanging the Christmas lights this year.
-没错了  -宝宝醒了
- Yeah. ‭- Babies are up.
没人去管管吗
Somebody gonna take care of that?
当你躺在斯黛拉的狗床上
When you lie down in a Dog Bed by Stella,
你会感到被爱环抱
you know you're loved.
有好一点吗
Was that any better?
怎么说呢  怎么说呢
Where to begin, where to begin...
你见过狗  对吧
You've met a dog, right?
是啊
Yes.
而且我知道你以前被爱环抱过
And I know you've felt loved before.
那把这两种思路合在一起  这一次尽量做好
So let's link those two ideas and try to get it this time.
我能先喝点水吗
Can I get some water first?
可以吧
I suppose.
你应该让她从狗盆里喝水
You should make her drink it out of a dog bowl.
那有点过分了  但你说得对
That seems over-the-line, but you were right.
这么做确实有用
This is working.
你好  艾丽克斯  我现在有点忙
Hey, Alex. Kinda in the middle of something.
好吧  就是想告诉你这边的事情
Okay. It's just that things are spiraling
有点不受控制
a little bit down here.
这个叫英格瓦的人  一直送我自己杀掉的东西
This guy, Yngvar, keeps trying to woo me
来讨我欢心
with things he's killed.
又一条鱼  谢谢
Another fish. Thanks.
那我把它跟之前的放一起
I'll...put it with the others.
我们怎么还停在这一步  时间不等人
We're still at this? Meter's running.
准备  开始
And...action.
当你躺在斯黛拉的狗床上
When you lie down in a Dog Bed by Stella,
你会感到被爱环抱
you know you're loved.
太棒了
Wow.
把她治到服服帖帖了
You have her right where you want her.
现在过去  给她一点赞美
Now, go in there, give her a little praise,
就能把她钓到你身边
and then reel her in.
这不难
It won't be hard.
这是继有一次即兴表演的观众让她扮
This is her best performance
跟她长得像的名人后  她最好的表演了
since that improv audience suggested "Jackee O."
英格瓦确实人挺好的
Yngvar does seem sweet.
我听说这边的自杀率也开始趋于稳定了
I read the suicide rate here has plateaued.
行了  可以了  结束了  孩子
Okay, that's enough. Wrap it up, kid.
准备回家吧
Time to go home.
太好了  谢谢你
Oh. Thank you.
这边真的不太行
This has not been working out.
我就是需要你的允许才好说出来
I mean, I just needed your permission to admit it
因为我来这里有一部分原因是为了取悦你
because part of me came down here to impress you.
回见啦  外公  爱你
See you soon, Grandpa. Love you.
怎么样
So?
非常棒
That was really good.
真是谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
这都是你的功劳
I mean, it's all you.
我从来没有遇到过如此老练的导演
I've never had a director with such a sure hand.
太有魔力了
It's so electric.
可不是嘛
It is, isn't it?
有没有兴趣去喝一杯啊  褐眼帅哥
What do you say we get a drink, Brown Eyes?
踏破铁鞋无觅处
It was all happening.
我离导演神作就只差一步了
I was on the brink of a directorial masterpiece.
这种作品可是能够让我一飞冲入
This was the kind of thing that could launch me
无薪实习的机会呢
straight into an unpaid internship.
这杯东西可以再稍等一会
Let's put a pin in that drink.
我想再试一遍
I wanna go again.
虽然只再重录了63次  但我成功了
It took 63 more takes, but I got it.
当你躺在斯黛拉的狗床上
When you lie down in a Dog Bed by Stella,
你会感到被爱环抱
you know you're loved.
你是"纯种"好演员  别表现像个小"杂种"
You're a purebred. Stop acting like a mutt.
再来一次
Again!
当你躺在斯黛拉的狗床上
When you lie down in a Dog Bed by Stella,
你会感到被爱环抱
you know you're loved.
应该还有隐含着痛苦情绪
There's pain behind this.
那些人类不经你同意就把你给绝育了
They spayed you without your permission!
这是你的身体  凭啥别人做决定  再来
It's your body! Who decided?! Again!
当你躺在斯黛拉的狗床上
When you lie down in a Dog Bed by Stella,
你会感到被爱环抱
you know you're loved.
-再来一次  -当你躺在斯黛拉的狗床上
- Again! ‭- When you lie down in a Dog Bed by Stella,
你会感到被爱环抱
you know you're loved.
卡  我们很满意
And cut! We're good in here.
你还有什么想尝试的吗
Anything you wanna try?
"试"也不是跟你试
Not with you!
垃圾  这是我正在看着的东西
Garbage. That's what I'm looking at here.
垃圾人类
Human garbage.
对  你说得对
Yeah, you're right.
就跟我妈说的一样  我就是个渣滓
It's just like my mom says -- I'm nothin'.
我要加入帮派  去弄个脸部刺青
I'm gonna join a gang, get a face tattoo.
我要卖头发去买毒品
I'm gonna sell my hair for nose drugs.
好了好了  停  我听不下去了
No, okay, stop! I-I can't take it anymore.
对不起  是我把雕像丢掉的
I'm sorry. I threw away the statue.
它...  它真的很土嘛
It was -- It was just so tacky.
各位  拜托你们别自暴自弃好吗
You guys, please don't give up on yourselves, okay?
你们还有大好未来在等着你们
You have very bright futures.
是啊  你说得对
Yeah, you're right.
当然有啊  在戏剧界
They sure do... in theater.
因为他们是学校的戏剧俱乐部
Because this is the theater group from school,
引人入胜剧团
The Emotivations!
棒  表现太棒了
Bravo! Brava!
我那天就在垃圾桶里发现了
I found this in the trash the other day.
我知道你肯定不会承认是你丢的
I knew you put it there and wouldn't admit it.
所以我带了一群才华洋溢的悲剧演员回家
So I brought some very talented young thespians over
来演绎迷途青年
to portray at-risk youth.
他抓到你啦  姐妹
He got you, girl!
我说了我想要跟这帮孩子建立情感
You know, I said I wanted to bond with these kids,
绝对是做到了
and I sure did.
这可是十分硬核的"捆绑"
We had some hard-core bondage.
你绝对会被炒鱿鱼
You're gonna get fired.
我疲惫的一身骨头躺在这床上就舒服了
This bed feels good on my weary bones.
等等
Mmm!
有骨头
Bones.
-我需要经费重拍  -做梦吧
- I'm gonna need money for reshoots. - Not gonna happen.
有时候人生中也要知道何时该投降
Sometimes in life, you've got to know when to call it quits.
投降并不总是简单
It's not always easy.
承认自己的错误需要很大的勇气
It takes a lot of courage to admit your mistakes.
你唯一能做的就是尝试从错误中学习
The only thing you can do is try to learn from them
并继续向前迈进
and keep moving forward.
好啦  直升机很快就要到了
Anyways, the helicopter will be here soon.
我想是时候道别了
So, I guess this is goodbye.
别出去外面等
雪怪是真实存在的
我也会想你的
I'll miss you, too.
你听到了吗
Do you hear that?
世上最美妙的声音就是婴儿不哭的声音
There is no sound better than babies not crying.
我们能睡个爽啦
‭Mm, we're gonna get so much sleep.
又或者...
Or...
又来吗
Again?
我感觉我能表现得更好
I just feel like I could do better.
你表现很可以了
Oh, you were fine.
真的吗
Really?
太好了
Yes!
晚安
Mm. Good night.
Good night.
什么  那是什么  那是什么
What?! What is that?! What is it?!
海莉  你在干嘛
Haley! What are you doing?!
我又把自己锁门外了
I locked myself out again.
这下好了  "感谢"你们的大吼大叫啊
Great. Thanks for screaming.
要不...  反正我们醒着也是醒着...
Well... as long as we're both awake...